urbandaddy.com 2015-12-09

# UrbanDaddy | Privacy Policy

UrbanDaddy Inc. ("UrbanDaddy") takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. It is the goal of UrbanDaddy to bring you information that is relevant and targeted to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for our email publication. Please read this notice carefully.

## I. PERSONAL INFORMATION

In order to distribute our email publication, we (obviously) need your e-mail address. So that we may provide you with additional services as well as more interesting and relevant content, we may request additional information, including your name, zip code, telephone number and credit card information. UrbanDaddy does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. URBANDADDY WILL NOT DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY THIRD PARTY WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT, EXCEPT AS DETAILED BELOW IN SECTION IV.

## II. NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, for example, annual income, buying preferences, and age. This information, also known as demographic and profile data, is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or personalize your experience at our site, in order to bring you more targeted and relevant content and to display such content according to your preferences. We may share this information with others, such as advertisers interested on advertising on the UrbanDaddy site but never on an individual level. This information will only be shared in an aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person. However, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

## III. USAGE INFORMATION

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, UrbanDaddy may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of our emails and our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently distribute our email publication.

## IV. INFORMATION SHARING PROVISION

UrbanDaddy may share information with carefully selected vendors and business partners with whom we work. This includes companies that offer affinity, frequent-user, and reward programs and sweepstakes prizing and sponsorship; and, companies that perform marketing services and other business operations for us (including providing goods and services to our users, as necessary to complete transactions you request). All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep all information confidential and to use the customer information only to provide the services we ask them to perform for you and us.

We provide services and products through third parties. These "Third Party Service Providers" perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service.

As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics do not include Personal Information. We may disclose Personal Information we collect from you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Site; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public.

## V. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS PROVISIONS

As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83, a California resident who has provided Personal Information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of Personal Information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure -- typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in some activity describes on our site. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific activity, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your Personal Information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide Personal Information on our site. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing info@urbandaddy.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address.

## VI. REVIEW AND ACCESS

You will have the ability to access the information that we have collected about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

## VII. CHOICE/OPT-OUT

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.

## VIII. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by our web advertising partners. Information about your visit to their site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

## IX. RFID TECHNOLOGY

At times, we may collect information from you at brick and mortar locations, such as events and pop-up-stores, using RFID technology, including but not limited to your name, email, and certain social media account information. This information will only be collected with your permission and after you specifically sign up to receive an RFID device, and may be used for the following purposes: monitoring specific, pre-defined activities and posting those activities to social media feeds. This information may also be shared with our sponsors that are clearly identified at such locations.

## X. TRACKING & THIRD PARTY COOKIES

You may have read about "cookies" or bits of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. As with most other Web sites, the UrbanDaddy Web site does use cookies to allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber, facilitate access to your preferences and present you with targeted advertising based on your previous interaction with our Web site and across third party Web sites. Such data collection and targeted ads are provided by a third party vendor, AdRoll. You can learn more about AdRoll and this method of advertising, as well as opt out of such targeted advertising, by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. Our Web site does not respond to or honor any web browser that does not track signals or similar mechanisms.

Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well. Unfortunately, we do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them.

## XI. IP ADDRESS

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may, from time to time, use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information and administer our Website.

## XI. PG-13

UrbanDaddy is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the website or receiving emails.

## XII. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As part of the service, UrbanDaddy may create links allowing you to access third party sites. UrbanDaddy is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

## XIII. SECURITY

We use physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to assist us in preventing unauthorized access, maintaining data accuracy, and correctly using your Personal Information. Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to your Personal Information to the employees, agents, and officers of UrbanDaddy who need the information for their jobs.

## XIV. MODIFICATION TO THIS POLICY

UrbanDaddy reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. Please note that continued access of UrbanDaddy will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

Thank you for taking the time and interest to review our policies at UrbanDaddy. If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of the UrbanDaddy Privacy Policy, please e-mail us. We welcome your questions and feedback. Please send all emails to: info@urbandaddy.com.

Thank you,

UD

Last revision on November 20 2013.

###  [ UrbanDaddy on Instagram ](https://instagram.com/urbandaddy)

[ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/_DL9GKSrYN/) 115 12hrs [ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/_ChoVpSrUL/) 92 18hrs [ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/_AofUmyrc0/) 147 1day [ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/-_6JwVyrRh/) 113 1day [ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/-9NSCdSrZf/) 200 2days [ ](https://www.instagram.com/p/-6of_aSrd_/) 113 3days
